accessgenealogy.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Access Genealogy

At AccessGenealogy, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (See [this article](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Privacy_policy) to learn more about Privacy Policies.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by AccessGenealogy and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, AccessGenealogy makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. In reality I’ve only used the log files to identify attempted hacking of the website. So if you’re not trying to hack us, we’re not using the log files to track you.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

AccessGenealogy does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on AccessGenealogy.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to AccessGenealogy and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on AccessGenealogy send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

AccessGenealogy has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. AccessGenealogy’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

### One All Social Login

OneAll Sàrl (“OneAll”, ”we”, ”us”) is a registered technology company offering a set of web-delivered tools and services for establishing and optimizing a site’s connection with many social networks and providers such as Facebook, Twitter, Yahoo! and LinkedIn amongst others.

The OneAll social optimization platform enables online businesses (“Developers”) to (a) easily connect their sites to all the major social platforms and integrate with Open ID and other external authentication providers; (b) offer their site visitors (“End Users”) on-site authentication, sharing and social features to enhance their connected experience; and (c) analyze a site’s social activity with helpful use data and metrics.

AccessGenealogy has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by One All Social Login. We do provide a means of registration using only a valid email address and password. You should consult the [privacy policy of OneAll](http://www.oneall.com/company/privacy-policy/) for more detailed information on their practices.

#### Facebook Login

We enable users to login using their existing (or creating a new) account with Facebook. Any information that OneAll has access to is disclosed during the signup process. We ourselves locally store the name, url, and email address assigned to your Facebook account (or a Facebook email address if you don’t allow Facebook to disclose yours) and a copy of your profile image. If you comment on our website, your profile image will be displayed next to your comment, and your name linked to your Facebook profile. This enables other users to contact you directly on Facebook if they wish. We never disclose your email address. If you like or unlike a page of ours, or share it, we record the fact that somebody liked and/or shared our content, but we do not know who.

### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a piece of software that grabs data about our visitors. It’s something like an advanced server log, but on steroids. It’s the reason I don’t need to use our internal log files.

What does Google Analytics record?

  1. How did you come to AccessGenealogy?
  2. How long did you stay for?
  3. What kind of browser are you using?
  4. Are you using a mobile device?
  5. And quite a bit more.

What do I do with your data?

The tracking information allows me to better understand the kind of people who come to my site and what content they’re reading. This provides me better information about what to include on the website, as well as design decisions.

All of my activity falls within the bounds of the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html).

Want to opt out of tracking?

You can also opt out of Google’s advertising tracking cookie or use a browser plugin to [opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
